futuremarketinsights.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy Policy - Market Research and Consulting | Future Market Insights

  * Future Market Insights (FMI) is totally committed to keeping client information and personal data secure. We respect your privacy rights and safeguard your personal information at all times. We prevent the use and disclosure of personal information by our employees or any third parties and we require them to maintain security measures similar to ours with respect to such information
  * The FMI site uses cookies, which are pieces of information placed on your system when you visit a site. Cookies enable you to navigate between the web pages effectively, store user preferences, and enhance web experience. Users can change their browser settings to enable or disable the cookies.
  * We do not share your personal information unless we have your explicit permission to do so
  * All our employees, vendors and services providers are strictly required to follow our privacy policy, and we sensitize them regarding our privacy policy and compliances
  * We administer control over the collection and use of your personal information for informing you about our products and offerings that may be significant to you
  * We will update your personal information upon your request
  * We abide by the laws and regulations of the land where we conduct our business
  * Under certain circumstances applicable or required by law, we may be required to disclose client data or personal information without giving notice. You can unsubscribe your name from our marketing lists by writing to us at - [unsubscribe@futuremarketinsights.com](mailto:unsubscribe@futuremarketinsights.com)

**Changes in Policy Statement**

FMI may update this Policy Statement from time to time by posting an amended version of the statement on our website. Please refer to this page regularly to view policy amendments, if any.

## THINKING

Our latest perspectives on strategy.

Read our latest management thinking on today’s most critical business issues.

## Talk to our team on how we can help you.
